{
    "id": "cc1f5808518c43f4a4cd2f5a38880eb8",
    "title": "Mixed Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Put a coat .................................. before going out.",
            "description": "To put a coat on is to wear it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b3ac5794a8af43dc99c30b47deaf1535"
        },
        {
            "question": "The business was losing money, so they closed it ............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ad1ac24a4f94e60ad91ee79bc70c6f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going to the airport to see .................................... my friend.",
            "description": "To see off is to go to the railway station or airport to say goodbye to someone who is leaving.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6496ca92d694584b49d6db10f8f3d26"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is always a good idea to take .................................. travel insurance.",
            "description": "To take out travel insurance is to purchase it.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b0a8570f12f44efcb67beda5e58819e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor advised him to give ................................. smoking.",
            "description": "To give up smoking is to quit smoking.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ef6eaf9e7e246488ae6a2568c372f06"
        },
        {
            "question": "I make it a point to catch .................................. my sleep when I am on holiday.",
            "description": "To catch up on sleep is to sleep for an extra hour or two.",
            "answers": [
                "up in",
                "up",
                "on",
                "up on"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "e01bc90dbfcb4c8ba56271d030942069"
        },
        {
            "question": "Because of your irresponsible act, we got caught ................................ in a great deal of trouble.",
            "description": "To get caught up in trouble is to land yourself in trouble.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b170286c58c145b9b266fedce0e7e503"
        },
        {
            "question": "This achievement calls ................................ a celebration.",
            "description": "If something calls for something, it necessitates it.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3c6f91eccf1e49578d1548b762fc5a73"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her performance was amazing. I was blown .................................... by it.",
            "description": "When you are blown away by something, you find it to be absolutely brilliant. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5c3432182ec34b4fb290d0dbe512e156"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has come ...................................... a lot of criticism over the manner in which she handled the situation.",
            "description": "to come in for criticism is to receive it.",
            "answers": [
                "up for",
                "in for",
                "on for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8d3b7a313c144abbe08a93db06021c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I came ....................................... these old photographs while I was clearing up the closets.",
            "description": "To come across something is to find it by chance.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "95787662e68346e18f3d42f00e26d943"
        },
        {
            "question": "The company chalked ..................................... record profits last year.",
            "description": "To chalk up profits is to earn profits.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fbeb83a7ac23454d890eda8408618f14"
        }
    ]
}